The very first is the epiphysis.
一番最初は松果体です。
It's called the thousand-petaled lotus.
これは千の花びらを持つ蓮と呼ばれています。
It is the seat of polyvoyance,
それは多視点の座であり、
it is the ability to see God in everything.
あらゆるものの中に神を見る能力です。
While the pituitary gland is the seat of clairvoyance.
一方、下垂体は透視の座です。
In Asia, it's called the third eye,
アジアでは第三の目と呼ばれ、
which allows us to see the hidden side of things.
物事の隠された側面を見ることを可能にします。
It is responsible for secreting all these hormones for the body.
それは体のためにこれらすべてのホルモンを分泌します。
In India, in Nepal,
インド、ネパールでは、
where in alchemy, they will put colors on
錬金術において、色の周波数、振動、周波数によってこの腺を活性化するために、額に色を塗ります。
your forehead
額に
to activate this gland through the frequency of color, through
色の周波数によって、
vibration and frequency.
振動と周波数によって、この腺を活性化するために。
So that means, and this is very important,
つまり、これは非常に重要なことですが、
the eye is not only
目は単なる
a light sensor,
光の受容体ではなく、
but it is also a light emitter.
光の放出体でもあるということです。
Sometimes, a gaze can be
時には、その視線は
so deep that it can
非常に深く、
cause hormonal stimulation
女性や男性にもホルモン刺激を
in women, or in men too.
引き起こすことがあります。
So there are also angles,
また、顎の角度にも
at the level of the jaw angle,
角度があり、
it is also said to be an eye.
それも目であると言われています。
Eyes that lead you to look into your unconscious.
無意識の中を見るように導く目。
There are light sensors here.
ここには光の受容体があります。
So you also have the link with the parotitis that will occur.
また、おたふく風邪との関連もあります。
And also the link with parotitis and testicles.
そして、おたふく風邪と睾丸との関連もあります。
To green.
緑色に。
The ring finger, it is said to be the finger of alliance and
薬指は、同盟と内なるビジョンの指であると言われています。
inner vision.
内なるビジョンの指です。
The heart is also the seat of loving vision.
心臓はまた、愛のビジョンの座でもあります。
It is said to be the window to the spirit of man.
それは人間の精神の窓であると言われています。
The breasts are these
乳房はこれらです
the eyes of the emotional body.
感情体の目。
It's an astral body.
これはアストラル体です。
It is directly linked
それは直接関係しています
with the eyes, the ovaries
目、卵巣、
and the knees.
そして膝と。
The D3 vertebra
D3椎骨は
is likely
あなたの視力を
to alter your vision.
損なう可能性があります。
It's a vertebra that needs to be checked.
確認すべき椎骨です。
It can alter vision.
視力を損なう可能性があります。
While everything that is ovaries
一方、卵巣と
and testicles,
睾丸は、
it's a vertebra.
それは一つの椎骨です。
these are the eyes of the energetic body.
それらはエネルギー体の目です。
Ovulate has the same root
排卵（Ovuler）は同じ語源を持ち、
and gives the same energy as the word evolve.
進化（évoluer）という言葉と同じエネルギーを与えます。
The time of ovulation corresponds to the time of evolution
排卵の時期は女性の進化の時期に対応し、
of the woman and menopause
閉経は
at the beginning of physical maturity
肉体的な成熟の始まりであり、
to truly begin to evolve spiritually.
真に精神的に進化し始める時期です。
The elbows are the eyes that allow you to look
肘は、エネルギー体の後ろを見ることを可能にする目です。
behind the energetic body.
人生を進むために肘を使うと言われます。
We say "use your elbows" to get ahead in life.
肘で突く。
To give an elbow nudge.
膝は膝です。
The knees, it's the knee.
それらは肉体の目です。
These are the eyes of the physical body.
精神体、エネルギー体、肉体。
Mental body, energetic body, physical body.
それらは肉体、地球の目です。
These are the eyes of the physical body, the earth.
それは女性が他者との関係を確認する体の場所です。
It is the place in the body where a woman checks her relationship with others.
膝。
The knee.
私は自分の関係と、その精神も確認します。
I check my relationship and with her spirit too.
女性に膝を当てる。
To kneel to a woman.
かかとは、肉体の後ろを見ることを可能にする目でもあります。
The heel, these are the eyes that allow you to look behind the physical body too.
それは地球の最初の目です。
It's the first eye of the Earth.
私は目を置き、たくさんの情報を持っています。
I put my eye down, I have a lot of information.
これらすべての目は互いに繋がっており、
All these eyes are all connected to each other
あなたの肉体、エーテル体、アストラル体、
and carry memories in your physical, etheric, astral
そして精神体に記憶を運びます。
and mental bodies.
そして、
And vegetate.
これらのすべての情報を再び伝達します。
So not only was there already information passing through there,
つまり、そこにはすでに情報が流れていましたが、
but now it's all these memories of the eyes
今度は、これらすべての目の記憶が
that are also found in this whole scheme,
この全体的なパターンにも見られます。
and in your interpretation, in your experiences.
そして、あなたの解釈、あなたの経験にも。
So what are you going to do with this image
では、あなたに属し、このすべての歴史に依存しているこのイメージを
that belongs to you and is dependent on this whole story?
どうするつもりですか？
Genetic, karmic, current,
遺伝的、カルマ的、現在の、
and pure memory.
そして純粋な記憶。